Thank you for watching
ME
bq News!
We'll be back again this year with more news from the members behind the scenes of the past year's successes!
Tonight, Nogizaka bq news from June to December!
Two more suspicious friends, high tension at Iwamoto's parents' house
Kaki: Legacy will be found again this year
New encounters in the park across the street Ogawa buys adult jeans for the first time
Tamura Yumiki's good point found after flooding hotel with Sato change
KuromiI want to be blown away if it's such a senior wind Atsuto Yoda become No.1
Ito, take a picture that looks like a lie
Okamoto, there's no limit to how much you can get wrong Iwamoto, I'll thank you for your care
Endo, I can't bear the weight of love... That's the Nogizaka bq news for the year 2023!
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get a good look at them.
I'm a sophomore in college...
I'm in my second year of college... but I'm going to college... and I made two new friends.
Thank you very much.
I had one friend before, but now I have two more.
I went over to their house and made omu-rice for them.
Oh no, no, no, no, no!
It's a piece of head.
It's heavy!
This is omu-rice too, right?
No, it's not.
It's too heavy.
I don't know why it's got anything to do with bonds or friends.
I can't eat this!
This can't be happening!
It was the first time for me to cook something for people, but it turned out better than I thought it would, and my friends who ate it were speechless because it was so good, and they kept eating it for about 5 minutes without saying a word.
I know it doesn't taste good.
It's really delicious!
What do you think?
This is what a broken machine says after it kills someone.
"Kizuna, kizuna, kizuna." "Kizuna, kizuna, kizuna.
You're a real pal.
We are friends.
I'm gonna build an engine or something.
What kind of project is that?
They took my experience.
I'm so happy.
It really added color to my life.
Of course it did.
That's what I'm talking about.
You're not lying when you say that, are you?
It's not a lie.
It's a lie.
I wish I had your wish.
Me too.
Do you have friends?
She's got lots of friends.
I know.
Why do you say that so many times?
Because they all come to me.
Really?
Good for you, Lin.
But it's nice of you to take my picture.
I was scared, though.
Not at all like the one at Yoda's ryokan.
This one was scarier.
I could see it clearly.
Clearly scary.
Go on, then.
Okay, Mr. Yamamoto.
What's with this B-grade look?
You're still at home, aren't you?
Not now, right?
Yamamoto?
It's nothing at all.
I live alone.
It's been a while since I've been home.
I'm really close with my sister.
It was a cool season in the garden.
I was just playing in the garden.
What do you do?
I was doing something like measuring points...
Is there any kind of video or something?
Here it is!
It looks like he's here a lot.
A measuring point.
What's this?
I feel it.
It's beautiful.
It's a beautiful measuring point
a beautiful house
A house
Yes, it's a picture of the old Yamamoto house.
There's a pond.
It's a very rich garden.
The garden has changed.
It's been rebuilt.
It's like a lawn sheet.
It's a modern house.
I've always done a lot of measuring when I get excited.
I've always dreamed of doing that.
The truth is, when I go back to my parents' house.
I'm really amazing.
I'm the kind of person who likes to joke around.
I'm so happy when they laugh.
I want to make them laugh.
I make funny faces in the morning.
Well, that's a nice family.
That's nice.
Let's continue.
This is the boy who comes every year.
That's right... his little brother.
Younger brother.
2023.
I'm in the same pose.
It's true.
Is this for Mickey?
This guy's amazing.
And he's looking at a lot of them.
That's right.
Every time he's on a music show or something.
He sends it to me and says he'll find it.
And before he goes on live TV.
They also send me videos of their support.
There's a little bit of that, too.
I want to see the video.
If she does her best...
If she does well.
Oh, she's so cute.
Oh, my God.
This is a video of me finding her.
I'm gonna start finding her.
She's still kind of spaced out.
Oh, my daughter.
She's cute.
Here it comes.
Amazing.
She's adorable.
She's so cute.
He's so cute.
And the cheering feeling...
So cute!
So cute.
Opera glasses.
They're so cute.
I'm so glad we've done this three or four times.
It's like a growth record.
It's true.
Go on, then.
Okay.
I'll be doing the ceremony in September.
I thought I'd practice playing catch at the park during summer vacation.
I brought my own glove.
But I couldn't do it by myself.
I called my mom.
While I was waiting for my mom
I was walking around the park.
I saw an injured frog in the park.
I brought him home and welcomed him into my home.
What do you mean you met a new frog?
Yes, I did.
So I have three frogs at home.
Oh.
Oh, my.
This one's the newest addition to the family.
This is the one that grows up.
That's right.
What's that, a regular one?
Maybe we'll get a new one.
We'll feed him.
They're wild, so they only eat live insects.
So...
I'd pick them up and stuff.
What do they eat?
Crickets.
Live ones.
Live crickets.
I give them to them with tweezers.
The two crickets that were there are fine.
Oh, my God.
So cute.
They're so cute.
They'll live a long time.
I don't know. They've got their own unique faces.
The one on the right, right?
She looks like Hime-chan.
I kind of like her, too.
She looks like my mom.
This side.
I saw Hime-chan with a color like that today.
Oh, my.
Oh, no.
She called her mom on the way.
Yeah, your mom.
That's it.
Here we go.
What's this?
I bought them for the first time.
Adult jeans.
I've been wearing the same jeans since I was in elementary school.
That's why I only had children's jeans.
They were getting pretty tight.
But I wore them.
I was using them, but...
I thought they wouldn't fit the length of an adult's jeans.
I thought they wouldn't fit.
I tried them on.
I thought they were really nice.
I bought two of them.
I guess I'm finally becoming an adult.
This one.
It's so long.
I'm serious.
So long!
It's long.
She said it would look cute rolled up.
Then I took out my Opusen.
What's this?
These were for the kids before.
That's right.
He's growing up.
Wow.
I used to do this until recently.
I mean, this is when I was a kid.
This is in the sixth grade.
It's like my last school bag.
how many years ago?
About four years.
Four years.
Four years ago, or not much has changed.
For a moment I thought it was a lucky one.
I know what you mean.
I thought it was Tutuji now.
Now.
That's a good story.
It's a good story.
Ogawa always comes up with something good.
Every time he comes up with something good.
Go on, then.
I'm out.
This girl...
What's this?
During summer vacation in September...
I went to Korea with a friend.
We shopped till midnight.
We decided to take a bath at 2 a.m.
And there were three of us.
I decided to go to the market.
The bathroom and toilet were in the same room.
There were no curtains or anything.
There was a glass door that went halfway up.
You know, it's a thing.
But I showered as usual without really thinking about it.
I didn't think about it.
And when you get out, there's water all over the place.
There's no place to go, there's water everywhere.
Uh-oh.
It was just...
But I really couldn't handle it with all the towels I had left.
I couldn't...
All the way to the front door.
Oh, that's not good.
But it was really 2:00 a.m.
What happened after that?
I got an extra towel.
We all wiped ourselves.
Why didn't you all wipe yourselves?
You're so nice to help me. You're so nice to me.
It's all the way down the hall.
It's all over the hallway.
Do you have any pictures?
No pictures.
I shouldn't have been taking pictures.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
If I had taken any pictures like this, I would have done it myself.
I'm sorry about that.
What's this episode about Sakaguchi getting spilled on?
Oh, we went to Korea together again.
You love Korea.
We had lunch on the terrace.
Elegant.
There was a cup in front of me.
Ren-chan said, "It's a bug.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
It's all on me.
All of it.
So much that there's already a puddle here.
I took pictures.
I was so desperate, I was really regretting it.
I didn't take it.
I remember the hotel at that time, too.
I went in after Ren-chan, and there was already water.
It's not the hotel's fault.
Maybe.
That doesn't happen in Japan.
That's why...
I'm looking forward to it.
We went to Atami together in September.
Japan.
I'm the type of person who gets all the mirrors wet.
You know...
Wet the mirrors.
When I rent a bath at my house or something...
They are the type that water is everywhere.
I thought she's like that.
So I just figured that's the kind of girl she is.
I do whatever I want.
It's like, "Wow.
Oh, man.
The one for Sakaguchi wasn't a shower or anything.
He just sprays it on.
He's just trying to get rid of bugs.
Stop it!
And now, the November double! I found a place that's so nice!
There was a photo of a hot-spring heater that was all over the internet...
I think it's the third one in the third row...
I think it's the third one in the third row.
rare
Gaga Paga Gaga
factor All
Oh, my God! What is this?
This is really a bit too long, isn't it?
Look at this.
That's a riot.
It's a riot.
I was looking at my camera roll.
I also have a picture of Yumiki with a long neck in my camera roll.
I have a picture of that too.
Wow, it's long! You're right, it is long.
Which one is the neck sticking out in front?
That's her hand, that's her hand, that's her hand.
It's a long neck, that's for sure.
Yumiki has a long neck.
You have a beautiful neck.
She has a long neck, and like I said, her hands are really long.
Her hands are long, too.
I thought it was weird.
That's not the point.
That's not it.
You don't even need a selfie.
But I thought she has great style.
You're right... she does have style.
But Ariyoshi also said I looked like a bowling pin.
That's how I noticed it.
Like Mr. Himura.
I don't have one.
I can wear a V-neck?
Can I wear a V-neck?
V-necks make me look like that.
So I can't because I look round?
You're a reverse yumiki, Himura.
It's a reverse yumiki. It's a reverse himura.
That's right.
That was funny.
That was interesting.
Go on.
What do you want to be deepened?
Just after the first selection of parents
Mr. Mizuki invited me to dinner.
When we went out for dinner together, he served us a plate of congratulations for our first selection.
I said, "Thank you for giving me this special dessert.
I said, "Thank you very much.
I told him that I saw Kuromi served a plate for the first anniversary of the first selection.
He told me that he saw Kuromi served a plate for the first anniversary of his first term and thought of serving it to us.
I thought I would like to do the same for my juniors in the future.
YamashitaThat's right.
That's right.
You have a strong impression of Kuromi, don't you?
It's like, "Welcome to my world.
Like, "Welcome to my world!
You made the younger ones feel like seniors.
I wanted to give them a senior look too.
Happy Birthday on a plate.
I didn't know that until I was older.
Isn't it amazing that college students do this to their juniors?
But then he did it to himself.
I'm sure the younger ones would be happy to have it done to them.
Yeah, I guess so.
I'm glad.
I'm planning to go out to dinner with many of my juniors again this year.
I'd like to do that.
How are your juniors doing lately?
We used to go to the hallway before a show.
Do you have that kind of thing?
Today, we took a picture together backstage.
We talked about hair color.
Not even cute.
Your hair color is still a little off.
Nogizaka has rules.
I'm surprised you can't do this.
It's fine.
So I'll go with Kuromi when she starts going.
That's a good thing.
Rika is also a member of the Black Jitsu Society.
What's a Kuromitsu-kai?
But groups like Nogizaka used to form groups like that for a long time.
There's no such group now.
So there's only the Black Jitsu-kai.
That's not good.
That would make Nogizaka equal to Kurojitsu-kai.
Like Ishihara's Army.
It's true.
Let's continue.
October 1st.
What's that?
Ayame and I went to karaoke.
We decided what to sing for the first song.
We sang a song called "Zabun Zabun" as a unit.
We sang a song called "Zabun Zabun" for the first song.
When the score came out, we came in second in the nation.
We lost.
How is that possible?
I'm so disappointed.
I can't separate the real from the fake.
I sang for a couple of hours, and then before I left, I said, "Let's try one more time.
I won first place.
And I have the photos to prove it.
It's the real thing.
I see you scored a 92.
But the unit got their own.
That's great.
Now they're looking for a challenger.
It's gonna be crazy.
What's the timing on this one?
We went out for shaved ice together.
And then we went to work together.
We said we still had a few hours, so we went to karaoke.
But Ayame had never been to karaoke except with her family.
It was her first time with someone else.
With someone.
And since she was my senior...
She was really nervous.
But she had her tambourine and maracas.
We're going to win the first place with this.
We'll do our own song.
I want them to fight each other.
Next.
This picture is so fake...
Yamashita and I have the same day off.
We talked about going to Asakusa to eat and walk around.
shooting games and visiting shrines.
It's like we're on location.
That's right.
We were approached by a rickshaw driver.
He said, "How are you doing, ladies?
We enjoyed Asakusa so much we were like "Asakusa high".
Asakusa high!
We were like, "Hey, let's make out.
We got on the rickshaw.
The brother took us to various places.
He took us to various places and took pictures each time.
That's a really good picture!
It's so beautiful, isn't it?
The atmosphere is so nice!
It's so beautiful!
What's this?
They have such great expressions!
They're so strong!
Nice leader!
And your brother is like a real photographer.
Like a real photographer.
Like he's a real photographer.
We do this kind of work too.
Maybe he's a pro.
It's like a battle between professionals.
It's challenging.
We're like a free newspaper.
That's true.
They didn't even notice the pictures.
No, they didn't.
No, seriously.
Thank you.
The muddled love triangle finally comes to an end.
Now, on to the next thing...what a mistake...
When I went out with Ichinose Miki, we were both late.
I thought, "Oh no, oh no, I've got to get out of the house early.
But I thought she said it was going to be cold that night.
So I hurriedly put a pocket warmer in my pocket from the kitchen and left the house.
And sure enough, when night came, Ku-chan started saying it was cold.
I thought she thought I was at home, so I took out my pocket warmer and put it in my pocket.
It was a pack of dried bonito flakes.
Oh, so that's how it is.
I put it away and wondered what it was.
But it really looked exactly the same.
Once I got home, I cooled down and took a look at the photos of the bags.
I took a picture of the bags side by side, so please take a look.
The colors are the same
Red and white.
How can you go wrong?
What's wrong? Did you give him bonito flakes?
You didn't tell me at the time.
You were too embarrassed to tell me.
That's good.
They'll definitely make fun of me.
No, but if he finds out, he'll make fun of me later.
He's got dried bonito flakes... from the cold.
But he's taking the dried bonito flakes with him.
He said he was doing the right thing.
That's what they think.
No, this is not... this is... when we had the takoyaki party...
It's connected.
I thought he was using bonito flakes on a regular basis.
You're the type to pour it on top of the takoyaki.
This is so B-grade.
I'll continue.
Return gift? What's this?
I didn't get one.
I didn't get one from anyone.
As soon as the recording was over...
"I love you so much, it's painful," she cried.
I'm so embarrassed and ashamed.
But I'm totally fine with it.
I'm sorry that I didn't get it when I thought I would.
I think Sachiki-chan probably felt bad that she didn't get it when she thought she would.
That's why she came all the way to see me.
And she said let's go out for dinner or something.
I'm the kind of person who can't go out to eat.
Can you show me the measurement?
I can't, but only in my hometown.
I thought I'd ask her out sometime, so I decided to go out to dinner.
You went?
We went alone.
What did you eat?
Shabu-shabu.
I have a favorite Italian place.
But it wasn't open that day.
Was the shabu-shabu a lot of fun?
It was a lot of fun.
We talked a lot about work, and we had a lot of serious conversations.
We had a lot of fun.
I can't go out to dinner with you because I'm too busy being anxious.
Some of us get along so well that we go on trips together.
It's a strange relationship.
Okay, okay, next.
Here we go.
What the hell?
This is Miku Ichinose's story.
I'm not talking about the last minute. I'm talking about the last time we talked about it.
When she was on the Matsuboron tour, she started asking to touch my butt.
She started talking a lot.
I knew that Miku was affectionate towards various people.
But in December, she started to say some very heavy things to me.
Just recently, she told me that she hates the person who will marry Mr. Endo in the future.
That's what she said.
That's the scary thing about a good line.
So I thought, "Wow, that's really heavy.
But Miku is pretty serious about all the members.
That's a character trait.
I think Miku is the only one who is single-mindedly heavy.
I'm sure she'll never waver from that.
As a result, I've just realized that it's about the same amount of love.
To one and three.
To three things.
I'm so glad I did that.
Thank you.
On the contrary.
That's what Ms. Ichinami said.
Endo, you're like one of those heroines in TV dramas or girl's comic books.
You know, the kind of heroine who knows she'll never be taken seriously.
That's the kind of position I'm in.
That's why I know that.
If I get married to someone in the future.
I'm really pissed off at people who say things like, "Endo, you're mine.
I'm really pissed off.
To a future partner that I haven't even seen yet.
You wouldn't say that, would you?
No, because it's like being married.
I don't see it that way.
I'm not jealous because it's just me and Sakira.
Endo says that's what makes people like that.
I don't say it either.
Endo doesn't say much.
It's okay to like someone.
If you like him too much, he'll pull away.
Endo usually pulls away.
The Nogi Takashi B-Grade News Award 2023 is for two more friends of Hayashi's.
I'm going to give you a picture!
See, that's good!
I'm so happy, and I'm sure my friends are overjoyed too!
The bond between friends
If you're worried, I'll show Kubo, Yoda, and Ogawa to someone like that
But I'd also like you to take a look at Kubo's to be exorcised.
There might be something in there.
And Yumiki's snacks
I spent the New Year's Eve...
I put it on New Year's Eve.
Mizuki Yamashita's 2nd photo book shot in LA to be released on April 23
Famous scenes from the 11thyear BIRTHDAY LIVE are now on view!
Tickets for watching BIRTHDAY LIVE streaming are now on sale!
Hello, my name is Rina Hayashi.
My favorite place in the world is a family restaurant.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Bye bye!